A Guide to the Nelson A. Rockefeller personal papers, Ann C. Whitman - Politics, Series P FA351
Rockefeller Archive Center
- M General (Box 13, Folder 282)
  Morhouse, L. Judson (Mr. & Mrs.): 1962-1966, Chairman, New York Republican State Committee, Lake George Commission, personal correspondence. Morris, E. B.: 1967, President, Saratoga Raceway, NAR thanks for season passes. Morrison, Ben: 1971, Union Church Matisse and Chagall windows. Morrow, Carol: no date, thank you for Inaugural Ball tickets. Morrow, E. Frederic: 1956-1959, White House staff. NAR's note of recommendation. Morrow, Walter (Mrs.): 1967, thank you to NAR. Morton, Thurston B.: 1959-1967, U. S. Senator, exchange of views on Vietnam policies. Mosler, John: 1966-1968, New York Urban League, personal correspondence. Mosmen, Arnold F. (Mrs.): 1964, Johnny's Fund, NAR contribution. Moss, W. F.: 1973, Assistant to the Secretary for Intergovernmental Affairs, Clinton County emergency loan assistance due to rainfall, declined. Mott, Stewart: 1968, requests appointment. Moylan, Neal L.: 1967-1970, Commissioner, NY State Department of Commerce, Brooklyn Navy Yard, Expo '67. Mrak, Emil M. (Dr.): 1969, Office of the Chancellor, University of California, Davis. Mueller, Merrill: 1968, American Broadcasting Company. Muganero, Francis J.: 1973, Bishop of Brooklyn, thanks NAR for note on his fifth anniversary as Bishop. Muir, Malcolm: 1959, Chairman of the Board, "Newsweek," invitation to NAR for informal meeting. Murphy, Robert: 1965-1969, resignation as member of The Fifth Avenue Club, thank you.
- M General (Box 13, Folder 0282A)
- MacCormick, Austin, 1971 (Box 13, Folder 283)
  Executive Director, The Osborne Association, Inc., service on Goldman panel investigating Attica riots.
- MacIntyre, Malcolm A. (Mrs.), 1972 (Box 13, Folder 284)
  Proposal for United Nations Day at Pocantico, declined.
- Maginnes, Nancy, 1973 (Box 13, Folder 285)
  Markel prospectus.
- Mahoney, David, 1972 (Box 13, Folder 286)
  President, American Revolution Bicentennial Commission, background information.
- Mahoney, Walter J., 1959-1973 (Box 13, Folder 287)
  State Senator, legislative sessions, National Conference on Aging at Ann Arbor, Diefendorf Committee, Executive Committee meeting, National Conference, designation of Mahoney to Thruway Authority, appraisal of NAR's visit to Buffalo, letter on Agnew's resignation.
- Maiorana, Ronald, 1972-1973 (Box 13, Folder 288)
  Press Secretary to NAR.
- Malik, Charles (Dr.), 1973 (Box 13, Folder 289)
  Lebanon.
- Mangum, Robert J., 1970 (Box 13, Folder 290)
  Commissioner, New York State Division of Human Rights, budget and lack of personnel problems.
- Manning, Bayless, 1973 (Box 13, Folder 291)
  Council on Foreign Relations, Inc., Annual Giving Fund Drive.
- Markel, Lester, 1973 (Box 13, Folder 292)
  Seeks support for seminars.
- Marshall, Alton G., 1967-1971 (Box 13, Folder 293)
  Secretary to the Governor, President, Rockefeller Center Incorporated, position papers, personal correspondence.
- Mason, Edward J., 1970 (Box 13, Folder 294)
  Division of Communications, New York State Executive Department, Albany Centrex line.
- Mattina, Joseph S., 1973 (Box 13, Folder 295)
  Erie County Judge, declines to run for Mayor of Buffalo.
- Mauze, Jean and Abby Rockefeller, 1959-1973 (Box 13, Folder 296)
  Problems Woodbury Junior High School vs. thruway, campaign, inaugural festivities, photo of Winthrop Rockefeller.
- Mayell, Beulah Roberts, 1973 (Box 13, Folder 297)
  Thank you to Ann C. Whitman.
- McAniff, Mary, 1968, 1872 (Box 13, Folder 298)
  Republican Governors' Association resolution, mailing errors.
- McCall, Tom, 1967-1973 (Box 13, Folder 299)
  Governor, State of Oregon, Governors Mid-Winter Conference.
- McCrary, John Reagan (Tex), 1967-1973 (Box 13, Folder 300)
  Sends "Newsweek" article, campaign suggestions, personal correspondence.
- McCulloch, Norman E. (Jr.), 1973 (Box 13, Folder 301)
  Dartmouth Alumni Fund, thanks for NAR contribution.
- McGrath, Diane, 1973 (Box 13, Folder 302)
  Seeks appointment to Racing Commission, declined.
- McGrath, Jack, 1972 (Box 13, Folder 303)
  Knapp Commission recommendation.
- McHugh, Keith S., 1959-1973 (Box 13, Folder 304)
  Commissioner, New York State Department of Commerce, NAR Presidential campaign; Report: Summary of Federal Programs, Special Cabinet Committee on City Problems, Third National Conference on Commissions on the Status of Women, Far East and Asia promotion of commerce, resignation, "Action for Transportation in New York State," recommendation on Michael Verboff for Governor's Art committees, McHugh appointed Director, State Science and Technology Foundation.
- McKay, Robert B., 1972 (Box 13, Folder 305)
  Chairman, New York State Special Commission on Attica.
- McManus, Robert, 1959-1969 (Box 13, Folder 306)
  Executive Assistant to the Governor, Federal legislation, Polish community, Christmas party Executive Chamber, radio program, Workmen's Compensation Commission, campaign trip to Buffalo, editorial comment on Capital Punishment Bill, legislative session.
- McNamara, Robert S., 1964-1972 (Box 13, Folder 307)
  Defense issues, World Bank.
- Meany, George, 1968-1973 (Box 13, Folder 308)
  Appeal for George Wetzel, congratulations, thank you.
- Melady, Thomas P., 1969-1971 (Box 13, Folder 309)
  Brazil and Paraguay demonstrations, Attica.
- Mendelsohn, Robyn, 1971 (Box 13, Folder 310)
  British Broadcasting Commission documentary, NAR involvement declined.
- Menk, Anthony, 1965 (Box 13, Folder 311)
  Original musical score.
  Related Archival Materials note
  See also Box 25
- Mercado, Milton, 1973 (Box 13, Folder 312)
  Employee at 812 Fifth Avenue, NAR recommendation for application to Military Sea Transportation Service, United States Navy.
- Merrall, David F., 1973 (Box 13, Folder 313)
  President, Rhodes School, Goldwater Memorial Exhibition.
- Michaelian, Edwin, 1959-1973 (Box 13, Folder 314)
  Westchester County Executive, Westchester Board of Health, NAR's contribution, Annual Dinner Republican State Committee, General Electric Plant situation, General Motors situation, North Tarrytown, Playland investigation, State Highway Program. Also includes correspondence with Laurance S. Rockefeller regarding donation of Rockwood Hall property.
- Miller, Alan D. (M.D.), 1972 (Box 13, Folder 315)
  Commissioner, Department of Mental Hygiene, events at Willowbrook State School.
- Miller, Dorothy (Mrs.), 1959-1973 (Box 14, Folder 316)
  Art.
- Miller, Paul, 1958-1967 (Box 14, Folder 317)
  Gannett Newspapers, Transportation Bond Issue.
- Mills, Wilbur D., 1971 (Box 14, Folder 318)
  United States Representative, Arkansas, Intergovernmental Fiscal Coordination Act of 1971.
- Mintener, Bradshaw, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 319)
  Seeks appointment, declined.
- Mitchell, John, 1970-1972 (Box 14, Folder 320)
  NAR message to New York State Legislature, Federal aid to subways, restriction on campaign contributions in the Revenue Act of 1971, New York State Republican Assembly Campaign Committee vs. political organization, National Aeronautics and Space Administration Grumman contract.
- Moe, Henry A., 1973 (Box 14, Folder 321)
  Guggenheim Museum, State Arts Council.
- Morris, George Maurice (Mrs.), 1973 (Box 14, Folder 322)
  "The Lindens" 18th Century House and collection.
- Morrow, Hugh, 1960-1973 (Box 14, Folder 323)
  Press conference advice on Vice Presidential race, speeches, 1960, civil defense, narcotics program, Unemployment Insurance Appeal Board, Report to Nixon on Latin America, Peter Brennan, National Aeronautics and Space Administration, personal correspondence.
- Morton, Rogers C. B., 1970 (Box 14, Folder 324)
  Poll.
- Mosbacher, Emil, Jr., 1973 (Box 14, Folder 325)
  Commission on the Future of Horse Racing in New York State report.
- Moscow, Alvin, 1972 (Box 14, Folder 326)
  Meeting.
- Moses, Robert, 1965-1971 (Box 14, Folder 327)
  Chairman, Triborough Bridge and Tunnel Authority, blueprints for Long Island Sound crossing.
- Moskovit, Harold, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 328)
  Appeal for position with New York State.
- Motley, Arthur H., 1973 (Box 14, Folder 329)
  Chairman of the Board, "Parade," sends clippings.
- Moynihan, Daniel P., 1973 (Box 14, Folder 330)
  National Commission on the Future of America in its Third Century.
- Murphy, Franklin (Dr.), 1972 (Box 14, Folder 331)
  Chairman, "Times Mirror", Los Angeles, California; NAR thanks for books.
- Murphy, Joseph H., 1959 (Box 14, Folder 332)
  Commissioner, New York State Department of Taxation and Finance, thanks for NAR autographed photo, President Kennedy's 1963 Tax Bill, New York State Lottery.
- Muskie, Edmund S., 1973 (Box 14, Folder 333)
  Legislation regarding General Clarke.
- N General (Box 14, Folder 334)
  Nagle, George: 1962, Iowa Republican Chairman. Nakamura, Gaiji: 1963, congratulations on NAR marriage. Nathan, Theodore R.: 1959, Assistant to the President of the Board of Education, New York City. Nelson, Philip: 1967, lends primative art. Neuberger, Roy: 1967, Neuberger Museum at State University of New York at Purchase. Nevin, David: 1965, "Life" magazine. Newhouse, Samuel I.: 1959, "Newark Star-Ledger." Newman, Bernard (Mr. & Mrs.): 1958-1967, NAR friends. Nicholson, Joseph L.: 1964, President, Metropolitan National Bank of Syracuse (New York). Nickerson, Eugene: 1967-1969, Nassau County Executive, NAR for President draft movement, Long Island Rail Road problems. Nicosen, William J.: 1969, (United States Department of) Housing and Urban Development New Communities Program. Nielsen, Waldemar A.: 1961, Ford Foundation, sends letter from W. W. Rostow. Nieter, Temple: 1962, Darmouth friend. Nobel Committee of the Parliament of Norway: 1966-1967, recommendation for Peace Prize for Grenville Clark. Nolan, Howard C.: 1962, Albany Junior Chamber of Commerce. Nolan, William L.: 1961, meeting with NAR. North, Cecil J.: 1963, President, Metropolitan Life Insurance Company, offers services. Norweb, R. Henry: 1962, Cleveland Museum of Art.
- Nixon, Richard, 1959-1973 (Box 14, Folder 335)
  1960, 1968, 1972 campaigns, appointments, Committee on Critical Choices, politics, personal correspondence.
- Norstad, Lauris, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 336)
  Chairman, Board of Trustees, Eisenhower College.
- O General (Box 14, Folder 337)
  Oakes, George P.: 1965, inquiry on friend. Oates, James F.: 1973, National Chairman, Jobs for Veterans. Obregon, Oscar (Jr.): 1968, well-wisher. Odlum, Floyd (Mrs. & Mrs.): 1961-1968, NAR thanks. O'Donnell, Harry: 1966-1970, Deputy Commissioner, New York State Department of Commerce, politics. Oetrow, David: 1966, personal correspondence. Ogden, Alfred: 1959, NAR thanks. O'Neill, Charles: 1966-1967, U. S. State Department organization. O'Neill, George: 1971, family, NAR thanks. O'Neill, Lou: 1970, "Long Island Press," sends photo of NAR & Willie Mays. O'Neill, Paul J.: 1971, Morgan Guaranty Bank. Orr, Dudley: 1967, Romney presidential campaign. Osborn, Fairfield: 1966, President, New York Zoological Society, conference of New York City cultural groups. Osterman, Judge Melvin H.: 1963, Grand Jury investigation & NAR pressure for Osterman resignation. Ostrander, Charles W.: 1962, thanks to NAR. Ostrowidzki, Victor: 1966, book reviewer, "Albany Times Union." Ottinger, Richard: 1968, Robert Fitzgerald Kennedy's funeral, Hudson River Expressway. Ottoway, James: 1968, editorial writer, "New Bedford Standard Times."
- O'Brien, Donal C., Jr., 1971-1973 (Box 14, Folder 338)
  Urban Development Corporation, political campaigns.
- O'Byrne, The Rev. Mother E. M. (Box 14, Folder 339)
  Office of the President, Manhattanville College, property for college.
- O'Connor, Carroll, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 340)
  Actor's comments on "The Dick Cavett Show" about NAR.
- O'Hara, Almerin C., 1971-1972 (Box 14, Folder 341)
  Commissioner, Office of General Services, World Trade Center, South Mall.
- Orr, Robert, 1968-1970 (Box 14, Folder 342)
  1968 Campaign, Lipschitz art gift to State University of New York at Purchase.
- O'Shaughnessy, William F., 1967-1973 (Box 14, Folder 343)
  President, WVOX Radio, President, New York State Broadcasting Association, politics.
- Oswald, Russell, 1960-1971 (Box 14, Folder 344)
  Prison budgets & programs, Attica riot.
- P General (Box 15, Folder 345)
  Pace, Frank, (Jr.): 1967, President, International Executive Service Corps. Pacetta, Albert S.: 1967, appointment. Pages, Louis: 1961, Director, Food & Beverages, St. Regis Hotel, New York City. Paiewonsky, Ralph M.: 1967, Governor, U.S. Virgin Islands, advertizing for Virgin Islands. Paradine, Thomas E.: 1962, illness. Parker, Gertrude: 1962-1964, NAR thanks, condolences. Parkinson, Elizabeth: 1967, President, Museum of Modern Art, exhibits & finances. Paschal, Deedee: 1962, thanks to NAR. Paschal, Guy: 1962, Assistant Counsel to Governor, returning to private practice. Patino, Antenor (Mr. & Mrs.): 1971, NAR thanks for lunch. Patterson, Alicia: 1963, editor and publisher, "Newsday," appointment of Long Island Park Commissioner. Pauker, Guy J. (Dr.): 1967, The Rand Corporation, Far East situation. Pawley, William D.: 1966-1967, Operation Amigo, Latin America. Paz, Alberto Gainza (Dr.): 1959, NAR condolences. Peabody, Margaret: 1962-1963, politics, fundraising. Pease, Roland: no date, art collection. Peeters, Paul L.: 1967, book on U.S. Foreign Policy. Pegler, Westbrook: 1959, columnist, voter registration. Periconi, James J.: 1966, NAR letter to Dartmouth. Periconi, Joseph F. (Mrs. & Mrs.): 1966-1967, position in administration, personal correspondence. Peterson, Ronald: 1967, New York State Department of Commerce, Expo 67, health insurance. Peterson, Ted S.: 1966, condolences. Petri, Thomas E.: 1968, National Executive Director, The Ripon Society, appeal for funds. Phalen, Clif: 1967, Chairman, State University Board of Trustees. Phillipe, Gerald L.: 1963, President, General Electric, New York State business climate. Phillips, Colgate (Mrs.): 1959-1963, Westchester Republican politics.
- P General (Box 15, Folder 346)
  Pickens, Paul Jackson: 1963, Winthrop Rockefeller's 10th Arkansas anniversary. Pierce, Neal: 1972, "Today" Show comments. Piotrowski, John: 1966, Treasurer, Easter Seals, NAR contribution. Pittarelli, Anthony: 1963, Counsel fo Governor, resignation. Pittman, Blanche: 1960, cousin Tucky Guille. Pittman, Steuart: 1964, Assistant Secretary of Defense for Civil Defense, resignation. Plattere, Governor: 1961, Governor of New Guinea, search for Michael Rockefeller. Podell, Bertram: 1968, elected to U.S. Congress. Polier, Justine Wise: 1963, Domestic Relations Court, Wiltwyck School. Pope, Bayard F.: education fund raising, World Trade Center. Poole, Marjorie (Mrs. Lyman C.): 1966, Governor's Office Hostess, thanks, resignation. Porter, Allen: 1964, Museum of Modern Art reception. Porter, J. Erwin: 1966, artist, exhibition in Rome (New York), sends copy of "American Artist." Powers, Earl R.: 1966, Assistant to General Manager, Hotel Carlyle, New York City. Powers, Frederic B.: 1966, New York State Medicaid set up. Preller, Fred W.: 1961-1966, Republican State Committeeman, newsletter, Chairman, New York State Assembly Ways & Means Committee. Prendergast, Michael: 1959, Democratic State Chairman, against auto insurance rate increase. Prendergast, William: 1968, George Romney achievements. Presley, Elvis: 1967, NAR's visit to Metro Goldwyn Mayer. Prosper, George H. (Jr.): 1967, Director, Division of Fire Safety, New York State Office for Local Government, consultant in Venezuela. Pyle, Thomas: 1966, former game warden, Kykuit, ghost-written book.
- Paley, Henry D., 1973 (Box 15, Folder 347)
  Appointment to New York City Board of Higher Education.
- Paley, William S., 1968-1973 (Box 15, Folder 348)
  Chairman of the Board, Columbia Broadcasting System, scheduling of documentary on Rockefeller Family, Museum of Modern Art.
- Palmer, Charles H., 1966-1970 (Box 15, Folder 349)
  Assistant Secretary to Governor, Medicaid complaints, campaign fund raising.
- Patterson, Herbert (Mrs.), 1972 (Box 15, Folder 350)
  International Council, Museum of Modern Art, newsletter.
- Percy, Charles H. (The Honorable), 1961-1973 (Box 15, Folder 351)
  United States Senator from Illinois, Special Prosecutor, Latin America report, Republican Convention, condolences, Lindsay.
- Pedersen, Ronald W., 1966-1972 (Box 15, Folder 353)
  Program Associates, Susquehanna River Basin Commission.
- Perkins, Roswell B., 1959-1970 (Box 15, Folder 354)
  Counsel to the Governor, clemency, New York State Liquor Authority, hospital strike, resignation as Counsel, Chicago politics, 1960 Presidential campaign, metropolitan areas, health insurance, Federal Highway Project, John Fitzgerald Kennedy's walks at Foxhall Road, medical care for the aged, highway message, politics, University of Buffalo, South East Asia statements, Puerto Rican statehood, 1964 Republican platform, Romney campaign, appointment of judges, Senator Goodell.
- Perrotta, Fioravante G., 1963-1967 (Box 15, Folder 355)
  Deputy Superintendent General Counsel, State Insurance Department.
- Pfeiffer, William L., 1963-1971 (Box 15, Folder 356)
  President, Albany Savings Bank, 1966 campaign, illness.
- Pforzheimer, Carl, 1972 (Box 15, Folder 357)
  Education Commission of the States, appointment.
- Phillips, Michael, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 358)
  Luncheon for Governors' wives.
- Pierson, Robert L., Rev., 1965-1966 (Box 15, Folder 360)
  Christ the King Foundation, speaking invitation to NAR, psychiatric patient, 1969 Presidential campaign.
- Pike, Otis G., 1972 (Box 15, Folder 361)
  United States Representative, Pike's vote on revenue sharing.
- Pitt, Nathan, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 362)
  Dr. Huan Chen Cheng application for job.
- Pisani, Joseph, 1971 (Box 15, Folder 363)
  Appointment.
- Plaza, Galo, 1968-1972 (Box 15, Folder 364)
  Secretary General, Organization of American States, Kissinger, history of International Basic Economy Corporation, Venezuelan crisis, NAR report to Nixon.
- Porter, Robert W. Jr., 1970-1973 (Box 15, Folder 365)
  General, United States Army (ret.), Latin America, appointment.
- Poses, Lillian L., 1973 (Box 15, Folder 366)
  Personal correspondence.
- Prezioso, Sal J. (Dr.), 1971-1972 (Box 15, Folder 368)
  Federal-State, State-local government relations.
- Price, George, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 369)
  British Honduras (Belize).
- Price, Robert, 1967-1973 (Box 15, Folder 370)
  Executive Vice President, Dreyfus Corporation, North Atlantic Treaty Organization troop cuts, 1968 politics, Silvio Mollo for Court of Claims.
- Procaccino, Mario, 1972 (Box 15, Folder 371)
  Clarification of appointment.
- Pryor, Harold, 1970 (Box 15, Folder 372)
  President, United Transportation Union, Long Island Rail Road problems.
- Purcell, Robert W., 1959-1973 (Box 15, Folder 373)
  International House, State University of New York Board of Trustees, Penn Central bankruptcy, Metropolitan New York transportation, International Basic Economy Corporation, Cornell presidency.
- Q General (Box 15, Folder 374)
  Quinlan, Lawrence: 1963, sent photos of NAR. Quinlan, Suzie Hughes: 1963, thanks to NAR. Quinn, William F.: 1961, Governor of Hawaii, son's application to Dartmouth.
- R General (Box 16, Folder 375)
  Rader, L. T.: 1966, school automation. Rangel, Charles B.: 1973, U.S. Congressman, NY 19th District, thanks NAR for support on energy crisis legislation. Ransom, Floyd D.: 1965, businessman in Mexico. Mexican-American Cultural Institute. Rauch, Charles: 1959, sends article from the "Saturday Review." Reed, Clarke: 1973, Southern Republican conference Program Chairman. Reed, John H.: 1966, Governor of Maine, not re-elected as governor, looking for position. Redell, Don: 1959, Teleprompter Corporation, NAR thank you for gift and wonderful job done. Reeves, Rosser: 1961, Chairman of the Board, Ted Bates & Company, surveys re: re-election of NAR. Regan, Ben: 1964-1967, Commissioner, The Port of New York Authority, World Trade Center controversy. Rehder, Katherine E.: 1962, Executive Director New York State Nurses Association, NAR sympathy on hospitalization. Reid, Edith: 1967, clipping about NAR from "Providence Journal" (Rhode Island). Reid, Ogden R. (Mrs & Mrs.): 1961-1965, NAR congratulations on Helen Reid birthday, State University cultural center, site for State University of New York-Purchase. Reischauer, Edwin O. (Dr.): 1967, Harvard University views on the Far East situation. Reitemeyer, John R.: 1964, Publisher, "The Hartford Courant," NAR thank you for editorial. Remington, Thomas R.: 1962, NAR re-election. Renchard, William S.: 1966, Chairman, Republican National Finance Committee Luncheon, appeal for financial support of the Republican Congressional Boosters Club. Renk, Wilbur: 1970, visit to ranch. Rhodes, James A.: no date, Governor of Ohio, sends gifts to NAR. Richman, Saul: 1966, send clipping re: Rockefeller Brothers Fund. Riegelman, Harold: 1968, global safety. Riesner, Samuel G.: Apprentice Program training and development of youth for roles in government. Rigg, Gerald B.: 1966, campaign experience. Righter, James H. (Mrs.): 1962, 1967, Volunteers Tie Line meeting. Riland, Kenneth (Dr.): 1959-1971, Steel Companies Coordinating Committee, World's Fair Grounds, formation of Post-Graduate College, osteopathic objectives, Report: "The Conservative apparatus and the 1968 Republican Nomination," personal correspondence. Riley, Henry W. (Mrs.): 1959, campaign, sympathies on Mr. Riley's illness, World Trade Bank.
- R General (Box 16, Folder 376)
  Rippon, Geoffrey: 1973, Secretary of State for the Environment, House of Commons, England. NAR letter of introduction of John L. Loeb and Austin N. Heller, New York State Council of Environmental Advisors. Rivlin, David: 1973, Ambassador, Consul General, Consulate General of Israel, "Israel" book written by Prime Minister David Ben Gurion. Roadarmel, Kenneth: 1972, Executive Director, NY State Council of Churches, support for NAR abortion stand. Robb, Gene: 1965-1968, President, Capital Newspapers, favorable editorial to NAR, education, Board of Directors of the Saratoga Performing Arts Center. Roberts, Dollie: 1967, thanks to NAR for gift. Robinson, Gilbert A.: 1967, Hooper-McLendon polls, public relations. Robinson, Robert L.: 1964-1966, President, Foxhall Community Citizens' Association, sends history of 2500 Foxhall Road, by Mary Elinor Lazenby, safety of children crossing Foxhall Road. Rockefeller, Schuyler A. (Mrs.): 1962, "The Transactions of the Rockefeller Family Association with Genealogy 1905-1909," book given to NAR, sends his thanks. Rockhill, Vic E.: 1959, Accra Gold Coast, Ghana. Rodi, Karl B.: 1959, appointment. Rodgers, Richard (Mrs.): 1964-1968, invitation to opening night of "Avante," declined. Rodriguez, Chi Chi: 1970-1971, contribution of $1000 to St. Jude's Hospital Cancer Research from check received from NAR for playing golf, Christmas greetings. Rogers, Donald L.: 1967, Editor and Associate Publisher, "The Connecticut Sunday Herald," American Heritage Foundation, study of obstacles to voting. Rogers, Stephen: 1959, Publisher, "Syracuse Herald Journal," NAR fishing trip to Lake Oneida and discussion over budget and tax problems. Romualdi, Serafino: 1967, Author of "Assignment to Latin America." Roosevelt, Franklin D. (Mrs.): 1959, The Eleanor Roosevelt Institute for Cancer Research, Mrs. Roosevelt's 75th birthday, NAR congratulations. Roosevelt, James: 1959-1966, invitation to NAR to dinner, declined, seeks appointment. Roper, Elmo: 1967, Roper Research Associates, Marketing & Public Opinion research. Rosenbaum, Richard: 1973, Republican politics, Southern Republican Leadership Conference. Rosenberg, Gustave G. (Mrs. & Mrs.): 1967, thanks to NAR. Rosenthal, Abe: 1972, Managing Editor, "The New York Times," NAR complaint about article. Rosenthal, Louis A.: 1967, world peace to be discussed by Dr. Milton Hindus of Brandeis University, declined. Ross, Frank J.: 1967, architect, family used to work for John D. Rockefeller, Sr; seeks to meet NAR. Ross, John C.: 1963, Officer Student Company, sends Papuan knife. Rostow, Walt: 1962, Counselor, (United States) Department of State, Inter-American Defense College.